Guide to the New York State College of Human Ecology records, 1900-2017
Cornell University, New York State College of Human Ecology records,
- Series III. Committee Files
  - B. Educational Policy
    - Summary Report, Index of Minutes, Minutes: August, September, Analysis of Endowed Credits, Policy of the College of Human Ecology on Awarding two degrees at the same level, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Minutes: September, October, November, A Biology and Society Packet, Report on Revised Apparel Design Major, Minutes: Nov, Report on Academic Advising, 1980-1981, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Minutes: December, Agendas for Meetings, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Minutes: January, February, March, Final Report: Ad Hoc Committee on Basic Competencies in Communication for Undergraduate Education in the College of Human Ecology, Changes in the Course Requirements for DEA, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Minutes: April, Minutes, May, Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Index of Minutes, Agendas for all Meetings, Minutes: September, October 9, October 23, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Minutes: November 20, December 4, December 18, January 13, February 2, February 23, March 9, Recommendations of the Provost's Commission on Writing, Proposed Changes in Interior Design Curriculum, Proposed Exemption for Math Placement Test, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Minutes: March 23, April 6, April 20, May 4, May 18, Draft Report of the College Writing Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Index of Minutes, Annual Report- EPC: 1981-1982, Minutes: September 17, October 1, October 15, October 29, November 12, November 19, December 1, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Minutes: December 3, A Proposal to Establish a Ph.D. in Textiles in the Field of DEA, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Minutes: December 17, January 11, January 26, February 23, March 9, March 23, April 6, April 20, May 4, May 18, June 1, College Study on Undergraduate Education in Human Ecology, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Annual Report 1983-1984, Index Minutes, Minutes: September 26, October 10, October 24, November 7, November 11, November 21, December 5 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Minutes: December 5, December 19, January 18, February 2, February 16, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Minutes: March 1, March 8, March 15, March 29, April 12, May 8, May 24, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Index of Minutes, Institutional Studies in Human Ecology: Agenda for Fall 1984, Final Report: College Study on Undergraduate Education in Human Ecology-1983, Minutes: September 11, September 25, October 9, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Minutes: October 23, November 6, December 4, December 18, January 31, February 28, March 14, Proposal for Establishing a Master of Professional Studies in Health Services Administration in the New York State College of Human Ecology, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Minutes: March 28, April 25, May 9, May 23, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Annual Report 1985-1956, Index of Minutes, Minutes: September 11, October 9, October 23, November 6, November 20, December 4, December 18, February 5, Proposal for the Reorganization of the HSS Major in Human Ecology, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Minutes: February 19, March 5, March 19, April 16, April 30, May 28, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Annual Report 1986-1987, Guidelines for Cornell HDFS-SUNY Cortland Education Teaching Certification Program, Agendas for all meetings, Minutes: October 1, October 15, October 29 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Minutes: November 26, December 3, January 8, January 2, February 4, February 18, March 13, March 18, Changes in the CEH Major, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Minutes: April 1, April 15, May 13, May 27, June 10, Transcript of the April 15th Meeting, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - List of Members, Agendas for all meetings, Minutes: September 2, September 16, September 23, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Minutes: October 14, October 28, November 18, December 17, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Minutes: January 20, February 18, Correspondence Re: MHA Degree, HDFS Language Requirement, Gerontology Concentration, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Minutes: March 3, March 31, April 28, May 26, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Minutes: September 1, September 27, October 11, November 23, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Minutes: December 7, January 26, February 9, March 9, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Minutes: March 16, April 27, May 11, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Minutes: September 12, October 10, November 28, December 5, December 19, February 2, March 16, March 30, April 13, April 23, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Minutes: May 11, Minutes: September 6, September 20, October 4, October 18, November 1, November 15, December 6, January 24, 1989-1990, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Minutes: February 7, March 21, April 4, May 2, May 9, May 16, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Educational Policies Committee, 1991-01-1991-11 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Educational Policies Committee, 1992-12-1993-02 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Educational Policies Committee, 1992-03-1992-10 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Educational Policies Committee, 1992-11-1992-12 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Educational Policies Committee, 1993-01-1993-03 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Educational Policies Committee, 1993-04-1993-06 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Educational Policies Committee, 1993-09-1993-11 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Educational Policies Committee, 1993-12 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Educational Policies Committee, 1994-01-1994-09 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Educational Policies Committee, 1994-10 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Educational Policies Committee, 1994-11-1994-12 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Educational Policies Committee, 1995-01-1995-04 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Educational Policies Committee, 1995-05-1997-12 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Educational Policies Committee Annual Report (1997-1999); Memo (1980) and Minutes (Box 106, Folder 21)
    - Educational Policies Committee Minutes, 1998-2000 (Box 106, Folder 22)
    - Educational Policies Committee Minutes, 2000-2003 (Box 106, Folder 23)
    - Educational Policies Committee Minutes, 2004-2006 (Box 106, Folder 24)
    - Educational Policies Committee Minutes, 2007-2008-01 (Box 106, Folder 25)
  - C. Faculty Meetings
    - Faculty Meeting Minutes for the New York State College of Home Economics for the years 1925-1968 are in boxes 80-82 in collection #23-2-749
    - Faculty Meeting Minutes-New York State College of Human Ecology, 1977-1986 (Box 8)
    - Administrative Council Meeting Minutes, 1970-1977 (Box 8)
    - Faculty Meeting Minutes-New York State College of Human Ecology, 1968-1977 (Box 9)
    - Administrative Council Meeting Minutes, 1969-1971 (Box 9)
    - Faculty Meeting Minutes-New York State College of Human Ecology, 1986-1995 (Box 53)
    - Faculty Meeting Minutes-New York State College of Human Ecology, 1991-2000 (Box 53)
    - Materials handed out for discussion at faculty meetings, 1983-1988 (Box 88, Folder 16)
    - Materials handed out for discussion at faculty meetings, 1990-1992 (Box 88, Folder 17)
    - Materials handed out for discussion at faculty meetings, 1993-1997 (Box 88, Folder 17A)
  - D. Standing Committee
    - Contains lists of the members of the Standing Committees within the College of Home Economics/ Human Ecology, 1950-2000 (Box 47)
    - Human Ecology Standing Committees, 1983-2006 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Human Ecology Standing Committees, 1950-1983 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - E. Affirmative Action
    - Africana Studies and Research Center, 1969-1986 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - COSEP (Minority Educational Affairs), 1983-1987 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Minority Education Report, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Minority Issues, 1985-1990 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Minority Retention, 1984-1989 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Minority Admissions Policy Committee, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Minority Fellowships (Undergraduate), 1988 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Minority Faculty Hiring, 1988-1992 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Committee on Minority Education, 1986-1990 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Minority College Exchange Agreement, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Minority Student Visits, 1989-11 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Visitation Program with Southern University, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Visitation Program with Howard University, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Minority Recruitment, 1988-1989 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Minority Recruitment and Retention- Report of Ad-Hoc Committee, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Minority Issues, 1979-1984 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Minority Recruitment Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Minority Recruitment Committee, 1988-1991 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - "Crisis of Minority Faculty at Cornell" by Walter Cohen and Henry Gates, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Affirmative Action Committee-Correspondence, Memoranda, 1989-1990 (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Affirmative Action- Faculty Recruitment and Retention (1); Underrepresented Faculty Initiative Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Affirmative Action- Faculty Recruitment and Retention (Folder 2), 1989-1994 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Affirmative Action- Faculty Recruitment and Retention, 1989-1994 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Affirmative Action- Graduate Students, 1989-1995 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Affirmative Action Committee, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - Human Ecology Affirmative Action Plan Ricciuti Report, 1990-1995 (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - Affirmative Action Plans and Minutes, 1990-1993 (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - Affirmative Action Environment Subcommittee, 1990-1992 (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - Affirmative Action Committee- Correspondence, Memoranda, 1991-1992 (Box 65, Folder 28)
    - Affirmative Action Committee- Correspondence, Memoranda, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 29)
    - Affirmative Action Committee- Correspondence, Memoranda, 1994-1995 (Box 65, Folder 30)
    - Affirmative Action- Correspondence, Memoranda, 1996-1998 (Box 65, Folder 31)
    - Affirmative Action- Correspondence, Memoranda, 1998-1999 (Box 65, Folder 32)
    - Affirmative Action Plans, 1986-2002 (Box 65, Folder 33)
    - Petition signed by Human Ecology Minority Faculty, concerning the search for a new Dean, 1998-02 (Box 65, Folder 34)
    - Review of Minority Education at Cornell University, 1983 (Box 65)
  - F. College Organization and College Study Committees, For more records concerning the Reorganization of the College of Home Economics, see College of Home Economics collection, #23-2-749, Box 78 and Henry Ricciuti's collection, #23-13-2551.
    - College Organization Committee - Reports, Memos, 1967-1977 (Box 106, Folder 26)
    - Organization Committee Report to President James Perkins, 1968-06 (Box 106, Folder 27)
    - College Planning Document (1980); Department Planning Document (1981)--Discussed in Advisory Council, 1980-1981 (Box 106, Folder 28)
    - Task Force on Ecological Perspective, 1982 (Box 106, Folder 29)
    - College Study Steering Committee, 1982-04-1982-10 (Box 106, Folder 30)
    - College Study Steering Committee, 1982-11-1983-01 (Box 106, Folder 31)
    - College Study Steering Committee, 1983-02-1983-08 (Box 106, Folder 32)
    - College Study on Undergraduate Education on Human Ecology -Final College Study Implementation Committee, 1983-06-1984-02 (Box 106, Folder 33)
  - G. Academic Planning and Budget
    - Academic Planning and Budget, 1980-1986, 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Academic Planning and Budget- overviews, attachments, 1994-1995 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Academic Planning and Budget- Human Development and Family Studies (HDFS) and Media Services, 1994-1995 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Academic Planning and Budget- Consumer Economics and Housing (CEH) and Design and Environmental Analysis (DEA), 1994-1995 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Academic Planning and Budget-Division of Nutritional Sciences (DNS), 1994-1995 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Academic Planning and Budget-Human Services Studies (HSS), 1994-1995 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Academic Planning and Budget-Textiles and Apparel, Urban Semester Program, Family Life Development Center (FLDC), 1994-1995 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Academic Planning and Budget-Consumer Economics and Housing, Design and Environmental Anlaysis, Human Development and Family Studies, Family Life Development Center, and Division of Nutritional Sciences, 1995-1996 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Academic Planning and Budget-Human Service Studies, Textiles and Apparel, Media Services, 1995-1996 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Academic and Planning and Budget-Consumer Economics and Housing, 1996-1997 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Academic Planning and Budget-Design and Environmental Analysis, 1996-1997 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Academic Planning and Budget-Human Development and Family Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Academic Planning and Budget-Human Service Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Academic Planning and Budget-Textiles and Apparel, 1996-1997 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Academic Planning and Budget-Division of Nutritional Sciences, 1996-1997 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Academic Planning and Budget-Media Services, 1996-1997 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Academic Planning and Budget-Mann Library, 1996-1997 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Academic Planning and Budget-Cooperative Extension, 1996-1997 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Academic Planning and Budget-Family Life Development Center, Bronfenbrenner Life Course Center, 1996-1997 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Academic Planning and Budget-effort distribution report, guidelines, 1996-1997 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Academic Planning and Budget, 1991-1993 (Box 105, Folder 8-9)
    - Academic Planning and Budget- Overview, DNS, and HDFS, 1992-1993 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Academic Planning and Budget- Textilesand Apparel, 1992-1993 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Academic Planning and Budget- Consumer Economics and Housing, 1992-1993 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Academic Planing and Budget- Design and Environmental Analysis, Human Services Studies, 1992-1993 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Academic Planning and Budget- Department Program Areas and Annual Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Academic Planning and Budget- Course Enrolment Trends, Faculty Effort Reports, Guidelines for Resource Allocations, Budget Worksheets and Annual Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Academic Planning and Budget-Administration and Bronfenbrenner Life Course Center, 1998-1999 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Academic Planning and Budget- Cooperative Extension, DEA, 1998-1999 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Academic Planning and Budget-Division of Nutritional Sciences and Family Life Development Center, 1998-1999 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Academic Planning and Budget-Human Development and Family Studies, 1998-1999 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Academic Planning and Budget-Mann Library, 1998-1999 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Academic Planning and Budget-Media Services, 1998-1999 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Academic Planning and Budget-Policy Analysis and Management, 1998-1999 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Academic Planning and Budget-Textiles and Apparel, 1998-1999 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Academic Planning and Budget-CAD, Cooperative Extension, Program Budget Conference, 1998-1999 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Academic Planning and Budgeting-Budget Requests, Board of Trustees Budget Plan, 1998-1999 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Academic Planning and Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 45, Folder 35-37)
    - Academic Planning and Budget, 1997-1998 (Box 87)
    - Academic Planning and Budget, 1999-2004 (Box 89, Folder 1-33)
    - Academic Planning and Budget, 2004-2006 (Box 90, Folder 1-13)
  - H. Communications Working Group
    - Communications Work Group, 1991-1993 (Box 106, Folder 34)
  - I. External Relations Committee
    - External Relations Committee, 1986-1990 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - External Relations Committee, 1988-1990 (Box 106, Folder 35)
  - J. Morale Committee
    - Ad Hoc Morale Committee, 1972 (Box 106, Folder 53)
  - K. Quality Improvement Process (QIP)
    - QIP Memos, 1992-1994 (Box 106, Folder 36)
    - QIP Presentation, 1993 (Box 106, Folder 37)
    - QIP Student Advising Team - Final Report, 1995-02-09 (Box 106, Folder 38)
      Includes photograph of advising team
  - L. Undergraduate Education
    - Committee on Undergraduate Education, 1969 (Box 106, Folder 38A)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Education - Learning Skills Center and Women's Studies Courses, 1972-1974 (Box 106, Folder 39)
    - Undergraduate Advising Coordinators-Meeting Minutes, 1995-1997 (Box 106, Folder 39A)
    - Director of Undergraduate Studies-Meeting Minutes, 2003-2006 (Box 106, Folder 39B)
    - Undergraduate Ad Hoc Curriculum Committee-Meeting Minutes, 2006 (Box 105, Folder 52)
  - M. Diversity
    - ADMIN-COMMITTEE, Diversity, 2001 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - ADMIN_COMMITTEE, Diversity, 2000-08-2000-12 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - ADMIN-COMMITTEE, Diversity, 2000-01-2000-07 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - ADMIN-COMMITTEE, Diversity, 1999-08-1999-12 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Diversity Committee, 1990-2000 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Diversity Committee, 2001 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Diversity Committee (Folder 1), 2002 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Diversity Committee (Folder 2), 2002 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Diversity Committee, 2003 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Diversity Committee (Folder 1), 2004 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Diversity Committee (Folder 2), 2004 (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Diversity Committee, 2005 (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Diversity Committee, 2006 (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Diversity Climate Survey, 2004 (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Diversity Survey - College, 2004-2005 (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Diversity Committee-Flemmie Kittrell Lectures, 1994-2002 (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - Diversity Committee - Flemmie Kittrell Lectures, 2004 (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - Diversity Committee-Flemmie Kittrell Lectures, 2006 (Box 117, Folder 14)
    - Diversity-Art Competition Reception -CD #2148, 2009 (Box 123, Folder 34)
    - Diversity - Employee data, 2003 (Box 125, Folder 16)
    - Diversity - Initiative - Annual meeting, 2002-2004 (Box 125, Folder 17)
    - Diversity Committee, 2005-2006 (Box 125, Folder 18)
    - Diversity Committee - Archway project and Annual Report on the Status of Women, American Indians, Asian Americans, Black Americans, and Hispanic Americans, 2005 (Box 125, Folder 19)
    - Diversity Committee, 2009-2010 (Box 125, Folder 20)
    - Diversity Committee, 2006-2007 (Box 125, Folder 21)
    - Diversity Committee, 2007 (Box 125, Folder 22)
    - Diversity Committee cookbook project and Annual Report on the Status of Women, American Indians, Asian Americans, Black Americans, and Hispanic Americans, 2008 (Box 125, Folder 23)
    - Diversity Committee, 2008-2009 (Box 125, Folder 24)
    - Diversity Committee art comopetition and Flemmie Kittrell Lecture, 2009 (Box 125, Folder 25)
    - Diversity - Faculty Diversity Institute, 2009 (Box 125, Folder 26)
  - N. Grants Committee
    - College Grants Committee, 1980-1981,1982-1985, 1986-1987, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - College Grants Committee, 1994-2008 (Box 123, Folder 1)
- Series IV. Faculty Biographical Files-(See also Faculty Biographical Files in collection #47-10-3394)
  - Allen, Josephine (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Anderson, Carol (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Armbruster, Gertrude (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Ashdown, Susan (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Avery, Robert (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Avery, Rosemary (Box 54, Folder 2-4)
  - Babcock, Robert (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Battistella, Roger (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Bayer, Helen McMullen (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Beck, Sam (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Becker, Frank (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Beisdorf, Heinz (Box 22, Folder 6-8)
  - Beyer, Glenn (Box 22, Folder 1-5)
  - Birckmayer, Jennifer (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Blackwell, Sara (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Bloetjes, Mary (Box 22, Folder 9-10)
  - Blum, Madeline (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Boyd, Michael (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Brainerd, Charles (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - Brannon, Patsy (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - Brenna, Thomas (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - Briant, Alice (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Brink, Muriel (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Brumberg, Joan (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - Bryant, Keith (Box 129, Folder 11)
  - Burgoin, Alice (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Burkhauser, Richard (Box 129, Folder 12)
  - Bushnell, Allen (Box 129, Folder 13)
  - Butts, Orrilla Wright (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Bymers, Gwen (Box 24, Folder 3-4)
  - Campbell, T. Colin (Box 111, Folder 2-3)
  - Canfield, Richard (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Canon, Helen (Box 74)
  - Canoyer, Helen Gertrude (Box 24, Folder 6-8)
  - Carreiro, Joseph (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Casasola, Marianella (Box 129, Folder 14)
  - Cassano, Patricia (Box 129, Folder 15)
  - Cawley, John (Box 129, Folder 16-18)
  - Ceci, Stephen (Box 111, Folder 4-5)
  - Cherry, Florence (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Chi, Peter (Box 111, Folder 6-7)
  - Chu, C.C. (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Clemhout, Simone (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Cochran, Mon (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Coffman, Charolotte (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Condry, John (Box 22, Folder 12-16)
  - Cornelius, Steven (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Crowe, Natalie (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Cushman, Ella (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Dalton, Robert Hatcher (Box 24, Folder 13-14)
  - Danko, Sheila (2) (Box 112, Folder 1-3)
  - Davis-Manigaulte, Jackie (Box 129, Folder 19)
  - Dean, Christiann (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Depue, Richard (Box 129, Folder 20)
  - Deveruyx, Edward (Box 22, Folder 17-19)
  - Devine, Carol (Box 129, Folder 21)
  - Devine, Marjorie (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Dickin, Kate (Box 129, Folder 22)
  - Dollahite, Jamie (Box 129, Folder 23)
  - Doris, John (Box 54, Folder 5-6)
  - Dunifon, Rachel (Box 129, Folder 24)
  - Eckenrode, John (Box 111, Folder 10-11)
  - Elliott, Jack (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Engman, Herb (Box 129, Folder 25)
  - Erway, Dora (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Eshelman, Paul (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Evans, Gary (Box 112, Folder 5-6)
  - Evans, Thomas (Box 129, Folder 26)
  - Failing, Jean (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Fan, Jintu (Box 129, Folder 27)
  - Feathers, David (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Feldman, Howard (Box 22, Folder 20-23)
  - Fenton, Faith (Box 22, Folder 24-26)
  - Finkelstein, Julia (Box 129, Folder 28)
  - Ford, John (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - Frey, Margaret (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - Frongillio, Edward (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Galenson, Marjorie (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Ganzel, Barbara (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - Garbarino, James (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Garner, Clark (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - Garza, Cutberto (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - Geddes, Richard (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - Gerner, Jennifer (Box 119, Folder 9-10)
  - Gibson, Kathleen (Box 130, Folder 6)
  - Gillespie, Ardyth (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - Glahn, Raymond (Box 130, Folder 7)
  - Glick, Peter (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - Grazier, Kyle (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Greene, Jennifer (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Grenne, Katrina (Box 104, Folder 12-13)
  - Gu, Zhenglong (Box 130, Folder 8)
  - Haas,Jere (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - Hahn, Alan (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - Hamilton, Stephen (Box 111, Folder 14-15)
  - Haugaard, Jeff (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - Hazan, Cindy (Box 130, Folder 11)
  - Heck, Ramona (Box 104, Folder 14-15)
  - Hedge, Alan (Box 111, Folder 16-17)
  - Henderson, Charles (Box 130, Folder 12)
  - Hogarth, Jeanne (Box 104, Folder 16-17)
  - Holden, Margaret (Box 130, Folder 13)
  - Hollis Brooke (Box 130, Folder 14)
  - Hua, Ying (Box 130, Folder 15)
  - Jennings, Jan (Box 119, Folder 14)
  - Johnston, Frances (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Joyner, Kara (Box 119, Folder 15)
  - Kenkel, Don (Box 111, Folder 18)
  - Klippstein, Ruth (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Knapp, David (Box 54, Folder 7-8)
  - Kopko, Kim (Box 130, Folder 16)
  - Koslowski, Barbara (Box 130, Folder 17)
  - Kutty, Nandinee (Box 104, Folder 18)
  - Kuder, John (Box 130, Folder 18)
  - Kushner, Tamar (Box 130, Folder 19)